https://www.torontoplasticsurgery.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
MenuAboutAbout Dr. BrownPhysician AssistantAesthetic Nurse InjectorOur PracticeOur FacilitiesIn the Media CloseProceduresBreast SurgeryBreast AugmentationBrava AFT Breast Augmentation with Fat TransferBreast LiftBreast ReductionMale Breast ReductionBreast ReconstructionBreast AsymmetryTuberous BreastInverted Nipple CorrectionVectra XT CloseHigh-Resolution Ultrasound for Breast ImplantsBody ContouringAbdominoplastyBody LiftLiposuctionVaginal Rejuvenation CloseCellfina Cellulite TreatmentSculptra for Buttock AugmentationFacial SurgeryBrow LiftEar SurgeryEyelid SurgeryFaceliftMicrofat InjectionNose Reshaping CloseTransition-Related Procedures CloseMedical AestheticsInjectablesBelkyra (Kybella) Double Chin TreatmentBotox®HyperhydrosisJuvédermLip Augmentation with VolbellaPRP (Platelet-Rich Plasma)Redensity IRedensity IISculptraSculptra for Buttock Augmentation CloseLaser and LightHalo HybridTM Fractional LaserLaser Hair RemovalLaser RejuvenationMicrolaser PeelPhotorejuvenation / IPL / BBLProFractional Laser Resurfacing CloseFacial AestheticsBiologique Recherche Facial TreatmentsDerm-eclatEyelash GrowthMedical Grade FacialsMicroneedlingPRP (Platelet-Rich Plasma)SilkPeel DermalinfusionSkin Care CloseSkin TighteningEndymed 3DEEPEndymed IntensifThermage CloseCellfina Cellulite Treatment CloseGalleryShopOffers and NewsContactLocationsGeneral InquiriesBook an Appointment Close
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Toronto Plastic Surgery has always been and will continue to be, committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your personal and corporate information. As part of this commitment, we have established Privacy Principles to govern our use of customer and consumer information.
Principle 1 – Accountability
Toronto Plastic Surgery is responsible for maintaining and protecting customer and consumer information under its control.
Principle 2 – Identifying Purposes
The purposes for which customer and consumer information is collected shall be identified before or at the time the information is collected.
Principle 3 – Consent
The knowledge and consent of the customer and consumer are required for the collection, use or disclosure of customer and consumer information except where required or permitted by law.
Principle 4 – Limiting Collection
The customer and consumer information collected must be limited to those details necessary for the purposes identified by Toronto Plastic Surgery. Information must be collected by fair and lawful means.
Principle 5 – Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention
Customer and consumer information may only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was collected unless the customer and consumer has otherwise consented, or when it is required or permitted by law. Customer and consumer information may only be retained for the period of time required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected.
Principle 6 – Accuracy
Customer and consumer information must be maintained in as accurate, complete and up-to-date form as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is to be used.
Principle 7 – Safeguarding Customer and Consumer Information
Customer and consumer information must be protected by security safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity level of the information.
Principle 8 – Openness
Toronto Plastic Surgery is required to make information available to customer and consumers concerning the policies and practices that apply to the management of their information.
Principle 9 – Customer and Consumer Access
Upon request, a customer or consumer shall be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of their information, and shall be given access to it. Customer and consumers may verify the accuracy and completeness of their information, and may request that it be amended, if appropriate.
Principle 10 – Handling Customer and Consumer Complaints and Suggestions
Customer and consumers may direct any questions or inquiries with respect to the privacy principles outlined above or about certain practices by contacting the designated person(s) accountable for privacy at Toronto Plastic Surgery.
Privacy Policy was last modified:
May 28th, 2018 by Toronto Plastic Surgery
Book an Appointment
Ask a Question
Your Name*Email*
Phone NumberQuestions or Comments for UsNameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Patient Resources
Special Offers and News
Don't miss our special offers and promotions. Sign up today and get our quarterly updates straight to your inbox!
Full Name
Your Email
Consent
I agree to the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Breast Reconstruction Awareness (BRA) Day 2020 – Virtual EditionOctober 4, 2020
Summer Aesthetic EventJuly 14, 2020
Dr. Brown Interview: “Perspective from North of the Border”May 26, 2020
Offices: 790 Bay Street, Suite 410, Toronto, Ontario M5G 1N8Phone: (416) 323-6336 • Fax: (416) 323-6325
© 2020 Toronto Plastic Surgery  •
Website development and marketing by AR Studio
Legal Statement
Privacy Policy
